https://www.helixstudios.net/privacy/

Login
Join Now
Helix Studios Privacy Policy
Helix, Inc., including its wholly owned (directly and indirectly)
subsidiaries (hereinafter “Helix”) is committed to protecting the privacy
and security of the personal information of our customers, employees and
third parties.
This Privacy Notice highlights how Helix uses the information collected
through its websites, apps, and services.
1. Information We Collect
1.1 Summary
Helix collects many kinds of information in order to operate effectively
and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. We
collect information when you register, sign in and use our sites and
services. We also may get information from other companies. We collect this
information in a variety of ways, including from web forms, technologies
like cookies, web logging and software on your computer or other device.
We use information submitted through our websites or collected through
email or hard copy surveys to analyze the characteristics of our customers
and improve our services.
If you request information about Helix products and services, we will
collect your name, email address, phone number, and additional personal
information. We use this information to contact you about your request, and
to follow up with you about the products and services in which you have
expressed an interest. We will also send information to you regarding
upcoming Helix events, releases, and relevant privacy related news and
alerts. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time by
clicking on the unsubscribe link provided in the email.
Helix receives and processes information (in paper and electronic form) in
accordance with its clients’ instructions for the purpose of providing
services to its customers. At Helix, we recognize the importance of privacy
to our customers and we strive to safeguard any personal information we
receive and may need to use in support of our customers.
We respect each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and
use information we receive directly from you only in the ways disclosed in
this Privacy Policy. This policy does not apply to practices that Helix
does not own or control, or to individuals that Helix does not employ or
manage.
In addition, we provide appropriate employee training (and discipline) and
have internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of
our compliance with Privacy Principles.
1.2 Full Text
Helix collects many kinds of information in order to operate effectively
and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. Some of
this information you provide directly to us. Some of it we get by observing
how you interact with our products and services. Some of it is available
from other sources that we may combine with the data we collect directly.
Regardless of the source, we believe it's important to treat that
information with care and to help you maintain your privacy.
What we collect:
- Registration
When you sign up to use our sites or services you may be required to
provide information about yourself, such as your name, birthdate, e-mail
and postal address and postal code.
- Signing in
To access some Helix services, you will need to sign in with a user name
and password, which we refer to as your user account.
- Using our sites and services
We collect information that tells us how you interact with our services,
including the browser you're using, your IP address, location, cookies or
other unique IDs, the pages you visit and features you use.
- Data from other sources - We may get additional information about you,
such as demographic data we purchase from other companies.
How we collect:
We use a number of methods and technologies to gather information about how
you use our sites and services, such as:
- Web forms, such as when you type information into a registration form or
type a search query into a search box.
- Technologies like cookies and web beacons (Please visit Section 2 of this
Privacy Policy page to learn more about these technologies).
- Web logging, which enables us to collect the standard information your
browser sends to every web site you visit - such as your IP address,
browser type and language, and the site you came from - as well as the
pages you visit and the links you click while using our sites and services.
- Software installed on your computer or other device, which may send back
information needed to operate, update or improve that software.
Customer Data:
Helix receives and processes information (in paper and electronic form) in
accordance with its clients’ instructions for the purpose of providing
services to its customers. At Helix, we recognize the importance of privacy
to our customers and we strive to safeguard any personal information we
receive and may need to use in support of our customers.
Helix Customer Information
Customer Information is information we collect from you when you purchase
and contract with us to provide services or technology solutions. We will
ask you to provide the following information:
- Email address;
- Phone number;
- Personal information, including name, address, billing information (debit
or credit card number);
This is information is stored on Helix’s systems, and is used to provide
services in accordance with the applicable terms and conditions.
2. Cookies & Similar Technologies
2.1 Summary
Most Helix web sites use "cookies," small pieces of data that can be read
by a web server in the same domain that put the cookie on your hard drive.
We may use cookies to help us retrieve your preferences and settings; help
with sign-in; to combat fraud; and analyze site operations.
We also use web beacons to help deliver cookies and compile analytics.
These may include third-party web beacons, which are prohibited from
collecting your personal information.
You have a variety of tools to control cookies and similar technologies,
including:
- Browser controls to block and delete cookies; and
- Controls from some analytics providers to opt out of data collection in
web beacons.
2.2 Full text
2.2.1 Our Use of Cookies
Most Helix web sites use “cookies,” which are small pieces of data sent to
your browser by a web server. Upon subsequent requests, your browser will
send the cookie data to the same web server, or other web servers in the
same domain, when accessing the web site. Cookies contain data that can be
read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. That data
often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies
your computer but may contain other information as well. Here is an example
of a unique ID number stored in a cookie that Helix might place on your
device when you visit one of our web sites:
9ha56er983130kmrtsx6jjabseniu65sjdjnnu9
We may use cookies for:
- Sign-in and Authentication
When you sign in to a site or service using your account on an Helix web
site, we store a unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an
encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from
page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. When
you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. This is
commonly referred to as a “session cookie”. We also use cookies to improve
the sign-in experience. For example, your user name may be stored in a
cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie
allows your user name to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to
type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public
computer or do not want this information to be stored, you can select the
appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be
used.
- Site Analytics
We may use cookies to count the number of unique visitors to a web page or
service or to develop other aggregate statistics about the operations of
our sites and services. These analytics help us operate and improve the
performance of these sites and services.
In addition to the cookies Helix may set when you visit our web sites,
third parties may also set certain cookies on your device when you visit
Helix sites. In some cases, that is because we have hired the third party
to provide certain services on our behalf, such as site analytics. In other
cases, it is because our web pages contain content or ads from third
parties, such as videos, news content or ads delivered by other ad
networks. Because your browser connects to those third parties’ web servers
to retrieve that content, those third parties are able to set or read their
own cookies on your device and may collect information about your online
activities across websites or online services.
2.2.2 How to Control Cookies
- Browser Controls to Block Cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify
your browser setting to block cookies. Instructions for blocking cookies in
different browsers are usually available at each browser’s privacy
statement or in their help files or settings pages.
Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to
sign in or use other interactive features of Helix sites and services that
depend on cookies.
- Browser Controls to Delete Cookies
If you accept cookies, you can delete them later. Instructions for deleting
cookies in different browsers are usually available at each browser’s
privacy statement or in their help files or settings pages.
Please be aware that if you choose to delete cookies, any settings and
preferences controlled by those cookies will be deleted and may need to be
recreated.
- Browser Controls for “Do Not Track” and Tracking Protection
Some newer browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” features. Most of
these features, when turned on, send a signal or preference to the web
sites you visit indicating that you do not wish to be tracked. Those sites
(or the third party content on those sites) may continue to engage in
activities you might view as tracking even though you have expressed this
preference, depending on the sites’ privacy practices. Because there is not
yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, Helix does
not currently respond to the browser DNT signals on its own websites or
online services, or on third-party websites or online services where Helix
provides content or is otherwise able to collect information.
2.2.3 Our Use of Web Beacons
Helix web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons -
sometimes called single pixel gifs - that may be used to help deliver
cookies on our sites, let us count users who have visited those pages and
deliver co-branded services. We may include web beacons in our promotional
e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been
opened and acted upon.
Finally, Helix sites may contain web beacons from third parties to help us
compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our
promotional campaigns or other web site operations. These web beacons may
allow the third parties to set or read a cookie on your computer. These
companies may collect information about your online activities across
websites or online servers, however, we prohibit third parties from using
web beacons on our sites to collect or access your personal information.
You may be able to opt out from data collection or use by these third-party
analytics companies by opting out on their respective web sites.
2.2.4 Other Similar Technologies
In addition to standard cookies and web beacons, web sites can use other
technologies to store and read data files on your computer. This may be
done to maintain your preferences or to improve speed and performance by
storing certain files locally. But, like standard cookies, it can also be
used to store a unique identifier for your computer, which can then be used
to track behavior.
- Local Shared Objects or "Flash cookies"
Web sites that use Adobe Flash technologies may use Local Shared Objects or
"Flash cookies" to store data on your computer. Note that the ability to
clear Flash cookies may or may not be controlled by your browser setting
for standard cookies as that may vary by browser. To manage or block Flash
cookies, go to the appropriate settings page, currently to be found at
http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html.
- Silverlight Application Storage
Web sites or applications that use Microsoft Silverlight technology also
have the ability to store data by using Silverlight Application Storage. To
learn how to manage or block such storage, visit the Silverlight Privacy
Statement.
3. How We Use Your Personal Information
3.1 Summary
Helix uses the information we collect to operate, improve and personalize
the products and services we offer.
Customer Information will be used to provide the services and access to
technology solutions you have purchased and the corresponding support.
We also may use the information to communicate with you, for example,
informing you about your account and security updates.
And we may use the information to help make the ads you see on our
ad-supported services more relevant.
3.2 Full text
Helix uses the information we collect to operate, improve and personalize
the products and services we offer. Information collected through one Helix
service may be combined with information collected through other Helix
services to give you a more consistent and personalized experience in your
interactions with us. We may also supplement this with information from
other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies to
help us derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order
to customize certain services to your geographic area.
We also may use the information to communicate with you, for example,
informing you when a subscription is ending, letting you know when updates
are available or letting you know when you need to take action to keep your
account active. We may also use the information, if the law allows it or if
we have your express permission to do so, to contact you for sales or
marketing purposes.
We will use your Customer Information to:
- Provide the services and premium access you have purchased;
- Renew subscription-based services;
- Provide customer support. While providing you with customer support we
may also gather additional information from you to investigate technical
issues, and respond to your support questions;
- Communicate regularly with you about your use of the software and
service, Helix events and other industry or privacy-related news, and other
Helix services we believe may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of
receiving emails regarding Helix events and other Helix services by
clicking unsubscribe link provided in the email. You will continue to
receive notices regarding Helix software and technical services you
purchased, and privacy-related updates such as notification of new or
changes to existing privacy regulations
4. Reasons We Share Your Personal Information
4.1 Summary
Except as described in this privacy statement, we won’t disclose your
personal information to a third party without your consent.
Please see Other Important Privacy Information for details about when we
may disclose information, including with Helix affiliates and vendors; when
required by law or to respond to legal process; to combat fraud or protect
our interest; or to protect lives.
4.2 Full text
Except as described in this privacy statement, we won’t disclose your
personal information to a third party without your consent. Contexts and
situations where we may disclose your personal data without your consent
are:
- Within Helix affiliates and subsidiaries
- As part of a merger or sale of a business
- With vendors and agents of Helix
- When required by law or to respond to legal process or lawful requests,
including from law enforcement or other government agencies or other public
authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement
requirements
- When required to combat fraud or protect our interests
- To protect life and safety
Please also refer to section 11.2.2 to learn more about why and with whom
we share or disclose personal information.
5. Accessing Your Personal Information
5.1 Summary
Some Helix services may give you the ability to view or edit your personal
information online. To help prevent others from viewing your personal
information, you first might be required to sign in. How you can access
your personal information will depend on which sites or services you have
used.
5.2 Full text
Some Helix services may give you the ability to view or edit your personal
information online. To help prevent your personal information from being
viewed by others, you first will be required to sign in. The method(s) for
accessing your personal information will depend on which sites or services
you have used.
Each Helix web site may provide you with links to access, correct or delete
your personal data. You can also contact Helix by using a provided contact
form on the web site or by contacting the office of the General Counsel
(legal at helixstudios dot com). We will respond to requests to access or
delete your personal information within 30 days.
Accessing and Updating your Personal Information
To review and update your personally identifying information to ensure it
is accurate, contact us vial email: privacy at Helix dot com
Helix will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable
access to any of your personal information we maintain within 30 days of
your access request. We provide this access so you can review, make
corrections, or request deletion of your data. If we cannot honor your
request within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will be able to
provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to
this information, we will explain why we cannot do so.
6. Under Age Internet Users
6.1 Full Text
When a Helix site or service collects age information, it will block users
under 18. Users under age 18, or the legal age to view adult entertainment
in your jurisdiction, whichever is higher, are not allowed to view or
access any Helix website.
7. Communication Preferences
7.1 Summary
You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Helix sites and
services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive.
Depending on the respective service, you may also have the option of
proactively making choices about the receipt of promotional e-mail and
materials for particular Helix sites or services.
7.2 Full text
If you receive promotional e-mails from us and would like to stop getting
them in the future, you can do so by following the directions in that
message.
Depending on the respective service, you may also have the option of
proactively making choices about the receipt of promotional e-mail or other
promotional materials from particular Helix sites or services by visiting
and signing into the following pages:
These choices do not apply to the receipt of mandatory service
communications that are considered part of certain Helix services, which
you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service.
8. International Users - Applicable Law
8.1 Summary
Your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other
countries. Helix may transfer information to our corporate affiliates,
service providers, and other partners who process it for us, based on our
instructions, and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate
confidentiality and security measures. These partners provide us with
services globally, including for customer support, information technology,
payments, sales, marketing, data analysis, research and surveys.
8.2 Full text
Please note that the personal information you submit to us may be
transferred to the United States and other countries to be processed by us
in order to provide this Web Site, our technology solutions and services to
you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Policy. Helix may
transfer information to our corporate affiliates, service providers, and
other partners who process it for us, based on our instructions, and in
compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and
security measures. These partners provide us with services globally,
including for customer support, information technology, payments, sales,
marketing, data analysis, research and surveys.
9. Support Data
9.1 Summary
Support Data is the information we collect when you submit a support
request or run an automated troubleshooter, including information about
hardware, software, and other details related to the support incident, such
as: contact or authentication information, chat session personalization,
information about the condition of the machine and the application from
when the fault occurred and during diagnostics, system and registry data
about software installations and hardware configurations, and
error-tracking files. We use Support Data as described in this privacy
statement, and additionally use it to resolve your support incident and for
training purposes.
9.2 Full text
Support Data is the information we collect when you submit a support
request or run an automated troubleshooter, including information about
hardware, software, and other details related to the support incident, such
as: contact or authentication information, chat session personalization,
information about the condition of the machine and the application from
when the fault occurred and during diagnostics, system and registry data
about software installations and hardware configurations, and error-
tracking files. We use Support Data as described in this privacy statement,
and additionally use it to resolve your support incident and for training
purposes.
Support may be provided through phone, e-mail, or online chat. Phone
conversations or online chat sessions with support professionals may be
recorded and/or monitored.
Following a support incident, we may send you a survey about your
experience and offerings. You must opt-out of support surveys separately
from other communications provided by Helix, by contacting Support or
through the e-mail footer.
To review and edit your personal information collected through our support
services, please contact us by using our Web form or email address provided
above.
10. Payment Data
10.1 Summary
Payment Data is the information that you provide when you make purchases.
This may include your payment instrument number (e.g., credit card, bank
account number), your name and billing address, and the security code
associated with your payment instrument (e.g., the CSV or CVV). This
section provides additional information regarding the collection and use of
your payment information.
10.2 Full text
Payment Data is the information that you provide when you make purchases.
This may include your payment instrument number (e.g., credit card, bank
account number), your name and billing address, and the security code
associated with your payment instrument (e.g., the CSV or CVV). This
section provides additional information regarding the collection and use of
your payment information.
Payment Data is used to complete your transaction, as well as for the
detection and prevention of fraud. In support of these uses, Helix may
share your Payment Data with banks and other entities that process payment
transactions or other financial services, and for fraud prevention and
credit risk reduction.
When you provide Payment Data to us, we may store that data to help you
complete future transactions.
You may remove the payment instrument information associated with your
organizational account by contacting us. After you close your account or
remove a payment instrument, however, Helix may retain your payment
instrument data for as long as reasonably necessary to complete your
existing transaction, to comply with Helix’s legal and reporting
requirements, and for the detection and prevention of fraud.
11. Other Important Privacy Information
11.1 Summary
Learn more about
- Why and with whom we share or disclose personal information
11.2 Full text
Below you will find additional privacy information you may find important.
Much of this describes practices that are common across the entertainment
industry, but we want make sure you are aware of them. Please keep in mind
that this information is not a complete description of our practices - this
is all in addition to the other, more specific information contained
elsewhere in this privacy statement.
11.2.1 On this page:
11.2.2 Sharing or Disclosing Personal Information
Helix transfers information to our corporate affiliates, service providers,
and other partners who process it for us, based on our instructions, and in
compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and
security measures. These partners provide us with services globally,
including for customer support, information technology, payments, sales,
marketing, data analysis, research and surveys. In addition to any sharing
described above in this privacy statement, Helix may share or disclose
personal information:
- With other Helix controlled subsidiaries and affiliates.
- As part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.
- With vendors or agents. Specifically, we may share it with companies
we've hired to provide services on our behalf. Examples of these services
include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and processing
credit card payments. When we share information with these other companies
to provide services for us, they are not allowed to use it for any other
purpose and must keep it confidential.
We also may share or disclose personal information, including the content
of your communications:
- To comply with the law or respond to legal process or lawful requests,
including from law enforcement and government agencies or other public
authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement
requirements.
- To protect the rights or property of Helix or our customers, including
enforcing the terms governing your use of the services.
- To act on a good faith belief that access or disclosure is necessary to
protect the personal safety of Helix employees, customers or the public.
Please note that our sites may include links to third-party sites whose
privacy practices may differ from those of Helix. If you submit personal
information to any of those sites, your information is governed by the
privacy statements on those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy
statement of any site you visit.
11.2.3 Protecting the Security of Personal Information
Helix is committed to protecting the security of your personal information.
We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect
your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For
example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems
that have limited access and are in controlled facilities. When we transmit
highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password)
over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the
Transport Layer Security (TLS) or Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocols.
If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal
information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.
Do not share it. If you are sharing a computer, you should always log out
before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from
subsequent users.
11.2.4 Where Information is Stored and Processed
Personal information collected on Helix sites and services may be stored
and processed in the United States or any other country where Helix or its
affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. We take
steps to ensure that the data we collect under this privacy statement is
processed according to the provisions of this statement and the
requirements of applicable law wherever the data is located.
Helix may retain your personal information for a variety of reasons, such
as to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our
agreements, and as long as necessary to provide services. To learn how to
access your personal information, visit Accessing Your Information.
11.2.5 Changes to Our Privacy Statements
We will occasionally update our privacy statements to reflect customer
feedback and changes in our services. When we post changes to a statement,
we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the statement. If
there are material changes to the statement or in how Helix will use your
personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a
notice of such changes before they take effect or by directly sending you a
notification. We encourage you to periodically review the privacy
statements for the products and services you use to learn how Helix is
protecting your information.
11.2.6 How to Contact Us
- If you have a technical or general support question, please visit
https://www.helixstudios.net/preview/custsvc.php
?
to learn more about Helix Support offerings.
- If you have a general privacy question, or a question with regards to
this Privacy Policy, please contact Helix’s Office of the General Counsel:
legal at helixstudios dot com
Accessing and Updating your Personal Information
- To review and update your personally identifying information to ensure it
is accurate, contact us vial email: privacy at HelixStudios dot com
- Helix will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable
access to any of your personal information we maintain within 30 days of
your access request. We provide this access so you can review, make
corrections, or request deletion of your data. If we cannot honor your
request within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will be able to
provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to
this information, we will explain why we cannot do so.
Helix, Inc., including its wholly owned (directly and indirectly) subsidiaries (hereinafter “Helix”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the personal information of our customers, employees and third parties.
Helix sites include HelixStudios.com, HelixStudios.net, 8teenboy.com, GuysHangOut.com, GuysBang.com, SpankthisHookups.com, Spankthis.com and
MankindVideo.com.
